>> Brian Holt: 错误边界是挂钩无法执行的两个操作之一。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Error boundaries is one
of two things that hooks cannot do.
您不能在不使用类的情况下执行错误边界。
You cannot do error boundaries
without using classes.
所以这其实是一个非常重要的一个，所以我们来看看这个。
So this is actually a pretty critical one,
so let's go ahead and take a look at this.
因此，这些 API 响应中的一些可能具有
So some of these API responses
could potentially have
里面的错误对吧
errors inside of them, right?
我们不控制这个 API，是来自第三方，对，所以
We don't control this API,
it's coming from a third party, right, so
我们要小心处理错误和处理格式不正确的数据
we wanna be extra careful with handling
errors and handling malformatted data.
因此，错误边界将允许您捕获这些错误中的一些错误
And so error boundaries are going to
allow you to capture some of these errors
不要毁了你的节目对吧
without crashing your program, right?
因此，我希望您在此处创建名为 errorboundary.js的新文件。
So I want you to make a new file
here called errorboundary.js.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我现在就告诉你
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
I'm just gonna tell you right now,
这主要是码头的代码
this is mostly code from the docs.
>> Brian Holt: 我只保留 reactjs.org/docs/error-boundaries.html。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'll just keep the
reactjs.org/docs/error-boundaries.html.
好了我们要从雷法进口
Okay, we're gonna import React from React.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将从 @reach/router 导入链接。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna
import a link from @reach/router.
>> Brian Holt: 所以我要说，类 ErrorBoundary，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So here I'm going to say,
class ErrorBoundary,
那些看起来很奇怪的词中的一个
one of those words that looks
weird the more you look at it.
扩展数据块。
Extends.
我们一直在做 React.component 但是
So we've been doing React.component, but
我要展示你能做到这一点的不同方式
I'm gonna show just a different
way that you could do this.
您也可以在此处放置组件，例如，例如扩展组件。
You can also put ,Component here like
this and just say extends Component.
没错我们只是在抽离组件
Works the same way right,
we're just pulling out component,
这样做并不一定有好处
there's no necessarily
benefit to doing it this way.
你会看到很多人这样做
You'll just see a lot of
people do it this way.
只是想给你看这个
Just wanted to show you that.
>> Brian Holt: 好，我们会说状态 = hasError， false。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
we're gonna say state = hasError, false.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，下一个要写的东西是静态的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, the next thing
we're going to write is static
getDerivedStateFromError。
getDerivedStateFromError.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将返回 hasError: true。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're just gonna return hasError: true.
>> Brian Holt: hasError: true。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: hasError: true.
你可以更深入了解如何做到这一点，但我们不打算这样做。
You could be more sophisticated about
how you do this, but we're not going to.
然后我们就会在上面说 componentDidCatch 。
And then we're going to say
componentDidCatch that top one there.
> > Brian Holt: 我们将返回错误和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
we're going to get back the error and
关于该错误的信息。
the info about the error from that.
这些都是 React 方法。
These are all React methods.
现在我们要做的就是
And here all we're going
to do is going to say
console.error， ErrorBoundary 捕获错误。
console.error, ErrorBoundary
caught an error.
>> Brian Holt: 然后我们会记录错误和信息。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're just
gonna log out error and info.
但如果你有 Azure Monitor 或 Track JS 或 Century 之类的东西
But if you had something here like
Azure Monitor or Track JS or Century or
就像这样
something like that,
你应该把它送去分层联合伐木公司
you probably just send that off to
the tiered consolidated logging service.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们会说回来，对不起，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
then here we're gonna say return, sorry,
渲染，渲染。
render rather, render.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会说
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna say,
如果 this.state.hasError ，那么返回。
If this.state.hasError, return.
>> Brian Holt: 一个 h1 ，再一次，您可能在这方面有更好的 UI ，但是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: An h1, and again, you'd
probably have better UI around this, but
我们只会归还一个上面写着这个列表有错误的 h1
we're just gonna return a h1 that says,
there was an error with this listing.
>> Brian Holt: 链接到等号。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Link to equals.
我要带他们回家
I'm just going to have them link to home.
单击此处以返回主页或
Click here to go back to the home page or
等待 5 秒
wait five seconds.
>> Brian Holt: 为用户提供一些信息，比如，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So just to give the user
a bit of information, like hey there's
在这里发生错误我们会把你重定向到主页上
an error here, just so you know, we're
gonna redirect you back to the homepage.
>> Brian Holt: 否则，所有要做的只是通过所有
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Otherwise, all you're
going to do is just pass through all of
要穿过的组件对吗
the components that are coming through,
right?
所以它就像一个错误的边界坐在一个组件之上如果有
So it's just like an error boundary that
sits above a component and if there's
一个错误，它对它有什么影响，否则它是通过的吗 ?
an error, it does something about it,
otherwise it's a pass-through right?
所以你就会说回你的孩子
So you just going to say
return this.props.children.
>> Brian Holt: So this.props.子代将是它是否包含在
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this.props.children
is going to be whether it was contained
组件的内部。
inside of the component.
举个例子，我们在这里有链接组件，对吗 ?
So for example, we have the link
component right here, right?
链接的 " this.sprops.c童子 " 将单击此处，对吗 ?
The children, "this.props.children"
of link would be click here, right?
是你把它放进去的
It's whatever you put inside of it.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
所以如果我在里面有一堆组件的话
So if I had like a bunch
of components inside of it,
this.sprops.子代将是其内部的所有组件。
this.props.children will be all
of those components inside of it.
好，最后，导出缺省 ErrorBoundary。
Okay, and then last thing,
export default ErrorBoundary.
>> Brian Holt: 这是一种高级 React 用例权限吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's kind of
an advanced React use case right?
这并不总是对您有用。
This is not always going to be useful for
you.
我不认为我在 Netflix上工作的时候
I don't think the entire time
I was working at Netflix,
我们曾经使用过错误的边界
we ever used error boundaries.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 这很漂亮，就是这样打破的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is prettier,
that's breaking it up this way.
所以如果这看起来很奇怪，那就是它从那里来的地方。
So if that looks weird,
that's where its coming from.
这就是如何将其分解为多行的方式。
This is how you can like
break it into multiple lines.
>> 扬声器 2: 这样会捕获在其任何子代中发生的错误吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So this will catch an error
that occurs in any of its children?
>> Brian Holt: 完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Exactly.
>> 扬声器 2: 为什么要返回this.props.子代?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Why do we need
to return this.props.children?
>> Brian Holt: 始终必须在呈示方法中返回某些内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You always have to return
something inside of a render method.
所以如果我有这个
So if I have this,
有一种潜在的权利不会归还任何东西对吗
there's a potential right that this
wouldn't return anything, right?
这意味着它基本上是在吃孩子们。
Which means it would be
basically eating the children.
这种说法真的很奇怪，对吧 ?
That's a really weird way of saying that,
right?
但这不会让孩子们产生影响。
But it would not be
rendering out the children.
所以它要经过对，它必须要经过一些东西，然后再经过
So it has to pass through right, it has to
take something and then pass it through to
否则它就会被挡住在那里
the other side, otherwise it would
just be blocking it right there.